Kieran Morgan

kiemorgan@gmail.com

503-893-5123

2333 S McConnell Dr. Tucson, AZ 85710 I'm hoping to work for a forward thinking company that provides modern technological services in the IT or AV industry.

I love people and bring strong people skills to a field that is unfortunately, often times, lacking it. I'm a good multitasker and very reasonable. My problem solving abilities and strong work ethic make me a good leader in group situations. I am an MCP and fluent with both Windows and Mac OS operating systems including common productivity suites including Office, Adobe Creative Suite, il ife and iWork

I started my IT career in 1996. I supported over 200 Windows and Macintosh computers for the high school I graduated from. After proving myself during my junior year as the technical liaison's assistant, they hired me on full time.

After that I worked for a local manufacturing company, and although I dealt with fewer computers, the challenges were much greater. The company was always integrating the newest technology into their work flow. I supported a Windows Active Directory server, 12 workstations and, at that time, cutting edge mobile solutions in the mid 2000's. I was also the company's graphic designer, creating all company brochures, sales materials and catalogs.

My next opportunity (and current place of employment) was to an AV company that specialized in high end home theaters and home automation. I was well utilized as a home automation programmer, graphics designer for touch panels and user interfaces and photographer for our portfolio. My main job however, was as the system designer and installer for all IT integration and communication.

Over the past 6 years I have also run a small independent consulting company providing computer and AV solutions to residential consumers and SOHO businesses. The people I have supported over the past few years have become not only faithful clients and evangelists, but friends.

I would love to discuss my application further with you. I can be easily contacted by email or phone.

Thank you so much for your time and consideration. I look forward to hearing from you.

Sincerely, Kieran Morgan

Kieran Morgan

www.kieranmorgan.com kiemorgan@gmail.com | 503-893-5123

Objective

To bring solutions and overall positive experience to clients while providing Information Technology provider a forward thinking asset.

Related Skills

Focused, motivated, result oriented team leader with the goal of increased productivity. Applies natural leadership skills to develop and strengthen long lasting customer/client relationships. Adept at multitasking in fast paced environments. Strong work ethic, respect for people and strong social skills aid in customer support in all applications. Quick learner and thinker who easily adapts to new environments and situations.

Computer Skills

MCP: Microsoft Certified Professional

Proficient on Macintosh and Windows operating systems.

Extensive knowledge and background with both Apple and Microsoft products including servers, workstations and networking architectures. I also have experience with many suites and applications common in workplaces and studios such as Microsoft Office, iLife, iWork, Adobe Creative Suite, digital darkroom photo processing and

video editing.

Related Experience

Solve IT: 2005 to current

Owner,

Independent IT Solutions: Consult, set up, maintain and service Residential and Small Office networks and computes. Focused on helping clients become more efficient by embracing new technologies.

Area 51 Audio Engineering & Consulting: 2008 to current

Systems Integrator, Crestron Developer

 $\label{thm:lemma$

Integrated computer based solutions when necessary.

Mortex Manufacturing Co., Inc.: 2000 to 2008

Systems Manager

Helped Maintain hardware and software/server infrastructure for a 12 $\,$

workstation, 4 server network and satellite location.

Palo Verde High School: 1996 to summer 1999

Maintained 8 computer labs, led teacher and student computer

learning programs.

Education

Palo Verde High School: 1991 to 1995 Diploma in Three Years - Honors

Pima Community College: 1995 to 1998 Advertising Arts / Graphics - Certificate